股票  债券今天全部上涨
Stocks and bonds are moving higher....
莫妮卡  我们为什么看商业台
Monica, why are we watching the Business Channel?
因为我前几天看到有支股票
Because I was going by it the other day I saw there was a stock
是我名字的缩写MEG
with my initials, MEG, on it.
有时我得苦等两三个小时
sometimes I have to watch for two or three hours
才会再看到
before it comes up again.
但是看到的时候蛮兴奋的
But when it does, it's pretty exciting.
亲爱的  我看你是真的需要份工作
Okay, honey, you really need a job.
莫妮卡  说到这个
Mon, speaking of which,
爸说他认识一个人你可以去应征
dad says he knows someone you can call for an interview.
-是吗  -好了
- Really? - Ok, right there!
这是今天的第三个预兆了  第三个了
That's the third sign today. Right there.
我替在座的每一位  说一声"什么"
On behalf of everyone, I'd just like to say, "Huh?"
因为你刚刚说了"爸"
No, 'cause you just said "dad."
今天我不管到什么地方
And everywhere I go today
都一直得到叫我去找我爸的预兆
I keep getting signs telling me to go see my father.
像我来这里的时候
Like when I was walking over here
我经过一个小吃店(音同布菲)
and I passed a buffet.
这是我爸的姓
Which is my father's last name.
小吃店供应法兰克福香肠(音同弗兰克)
And they were serving franks
他的名字只差最后一个"S"
which is his first name minus the "s" at the end.
是的
Yes.
还有一家烤肉店  烤架上有鸡在转
And there was a rotisserie with a spinning chicken.
他的印第安名字吗
His Indian name?
不是  因为我上次临"机"脱逃了
No. Because I chickened out the last time...
就在上次去见他时
...when I tried to meet him.
巧合吗  我不认为哦
So I mean coincidences? I don't think so.
-奇哉怪哉  -怪透了
- Freaky. - Weird, weird.
最后一个汉堡谁要
Okay, so who wants the last hamburger?
好了  够了  我非去不可了
All right, that's it. Now I have to go see him.
为什么
Why?
汉堡  麦当劳
Hamburger? McDonald's?
麦老先生有块地  我爸是"低"头配药的
Old McDonald had a farm. My dad is a pharmacist.
老兄  我累死了
Man, I am so beat.
别去打什么壁球了  就在这里混吧
You wanna forget racquetball and hang out?
好吧
Yeah, all right.
那是我们的位子
Hey, you're in our seats.
抱歉  我们不知道
Sorry, we didn't know.
我们本来坐那里的
We were sitting there.
好吧  还有另外一种说法
Okay. There is one more way to say it.
谁知道
Who knows it?
你这是在说笑话吗
Was that supposed to be funny?
其实我在说多姿多采的话
Actually, I was going for colorful.
-这家伙怎么了   -你怎么了
- What's with this guy? - What's with you?
没什么  他没怎么
Nothing. Nothing's with him.
请慢用咖啡
Enjoy your coffee.
刚刚发生了什么事
What just happened?
我刚拿了你的帽子
I just took your hat.
你看  我也能妙趣横生
See, I can be funny too.
我的笑话就是拿了你的帽子
My joke is that I took your hat.
那真有趣啊
That is funny.
-能还给我吗  -不行
- Can I have it back? - No.
-不行  -不行
- No?  - No!
好的  好的
Okay, Okay.
你知道吗  我觉得你很风趣
You know what? I think you're very funny.
我真的好崇拜你哦
Kudos on that hat joke.
别这样  两位  把帽子还给他嘛
But come on, guys, just give him back the hat.
为什么
Why should we?
因为那是顶特别的帽子
Because it's a special hat.
有一天他的心情很不好  就买了这顶帽子
See, he bought it because he was feeling really down one day.
他用帽子
So he got the hat...
来帮自己打气
...to cheer himself up, you know?
-钱德勒  -闭嘴  现在就闭嘴
- Chandler... - Stop talking. Stop talking now.
让我搞清楚  你就这么抢了我的帽子吗
Let me get this straight. You're stealing my hat?
你有意见吗
You got a problem with that?
没  我只是想确定大家达成了共识
No, just wanna make sure we're on the same page.
面试结果怎么样
How'd the interview go?
逊毙了
It bit.
那是一家50年代主题的餐厅
It was a 50s theme restaurant.
我得穿戏服做菜  还得在吧台上跳舞
I have to cook in a costume and dance on the counter.
我以前可是"艺匠咖啡"的副主厨
I was a sous chef at Cafe des Artistes.
我怎能接受一个
How could I take a job where I have to
我得做"卷卷脆薯"的工作呢
make something called Laverne and Curly Fries?
-那就别做啊  -我怎么能不做呢
- Don't do it. - How can I not do it?
我银行里面只剩下127块了
I have $127 in the bank!
莫妮卡  放轻松  去拿瓶啤酒
Monica, relax. Go get a beer.
我不想喝啤酒
I don't want a beer.
谁说是给你的
Who said it was for you?
你们两个怎么了
What's the matter with you?
咖啡馆里有个坏蛋抢了我的帽子
Some mean guys at the coffeehouse took my hat.
-不会吧  -你开玩笑
- No! - You're kidding?
简直荒唐透了  这些人就是恶霸
It was ridiculous. These guys they were bullies.
是真正的恶霸
Actual bullies.
我们是成年人  不应该再碰上这种事了
We're grownups. This kind of stuff isn't supposed to happen anymore.
不  等一下  我孤家寡人
Oh, no, wait a minute. I have no one.
我们下去把你的帽子拿回来
Let's go down there and get your hat back.
算了吧  说不定已经被拆成零件卖掉了
Forget it. It's probably stripped and sold for parts by now.
-我涨了  -什么
- I went up! - What?
我的股票MEG  涨了两个点
My stock, MEG, it went up two points.
若我昨天把我的127元
Do you realize that if I'd invested my $127
投资在我自己身上
in myself yesterday...
那我今天就会比昨天有钱了
...that l'd, like, have a lot more than that today.
知道吗  我要放手一搏
You know what? I'm going to do it.
-搏什么  -拿钱投资我
- Do what? - Put all my money in me.
莫妮卡  你在鬼扯什么
Monica, what are you talking about?
你对股市一窍不通
You don't know the first thing about the stock market.
要通什么  买卖高低  熊市  牛市
What's to know? Buy, sell. High, low. Bears, bulls.
喂  曼哈顿
Yes, Manhattan.
麻烦帮我查个号码  股票
Telephone number for the stock...
商店的
...selling store.
你看  我就说带枕头来是对的吧
See? didn't I told you these pillows would be a good idea.
天啊
Oh, God.
就这样了
Here we go.
我这辈子第一次  要喊"嗨  生父"了
For the first time in my life, I'm gonna say, "Hi, Birth Father!"
-我们爱你  我们支持你  -一切顺利
- We love you. We're here for you. - Good luck.
谢谢
Thanks.
瑞秋  要不要三明治
Hey, Rach, you want some sandwich?
里面有什么
What is in that?
橄榄火腿加火腿酱  没涂蛋黄酱
Olive loaf and ham spread. No mayo.
是啊  涂了蛋黄酱就恶心了
No, because mayo, that would make it gross.
-跑  菲比  跑  -不要  狗狗  拜托
- Run, Phoebe, run! - No, no, doggy, please!
我想爱所有的动物
I do so want to love all animals.
拜托别咬  快走
Please, no. Back off!
给它骨头  拿骨头来  有没有骨头
Get him a bone, get a bone. You gotta bone?
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding?
看  狗粮  老天  够了
Look, kibbles! Bits! God, all right.
放开我的腿  你这个狗东西
Get the hell off my leg, you yippity piece of crap!
好了  我们碰上难题了
Okay. All right. We have a problem.
你出去拿走它的蹦床就好了
Well why don't you just reach out and take his trampoline.
我知道怎么办了
Okay, here, I know what we can do.
别
Hey,hey no.
狗狗  去吃三明治
Okay, doggy, get the sandwich!
去吃三明治啊  去吃三明治
Ok go get the sandwich, get the sandwich doggie.
好狗狗  去吃三明治
Good doggie get the sandwich, get the…
乔伊  它连自己都舔
Ok, Joey, the dog will lick himself
却不碰你的三明治
but he will not touch your sandwich.
这告诉你什么
What does that tell you?
-它不吃的话  我自己吃  -你疯了吧
- Well if he's not gonna eat it, I will. - Are you crazy?
菲比  它是只小狗而已
Phoebs, he's just a little dog.
-嘿  -干嘛
- Hey. - What?
一定要做21世纪的房地产经纪人
Do you have to be a Century 21 real-estate agent...
才能穿着那么酷的外套吗
...to get to wear those cool jackets?
你会跟女生这样搭讪吗
Do you say this stuff to girls?
那不是你帽子的旧主人吗
Isn't that the guy who used to wear your hat?
看他们坐在哪里了
And look where they're sitting.
你在说笑吧  你们才刚进门
You're joking, right? You guys just walked through the door.
或许我们说得不够清楚
Maybe we didn't make it clear enough.
这张沙发是我们的
This couch belongs to us.
这样吧  你们叫一声沙发
I'll tell you what, you call the couch...
然后我们也对着它叫一声
...and then we'll call the couch...
看它会到谁那里去
...and we'll see who it comes to.
我一直不懂  你们为什么还赖在这个地方
You know what I keep wondering why you two are still sitting here.
好了  够了
All right, that's it.
我受够你们了
I have had enough of this, all right?
甘瑟
Gunther.
这两个家伙想抢我们的座位
These guys are trying to take our seat.
两位  他们先来的
Fellas, these guys were here first.
抱歉  我们不知道
Oh, sorry, didn't realize.
好了
There you go.
谢谢  甘瑟
Thank you, Gunther.
是你们逼我们这么做的
We didn't want to have to go and do that.
他打小报告
He told on us?
你打小报告
You told on us?
伙计  你们逼得我别无选择
Well, pal, you didn't give me much of a choice.
-别玩他的东西  -我知道
- Don't play with his thing. - I know.
很好
All right.
我们到外面解决
Let's take this outside.
"我们到外面解决"
"Let's take this outside?"
谁会这么说
Who talks like that?
即将要痛扁你们的人会这么说
The guy who's about to kick your ass talks like that.
谁叫你多嘴呢
You had to ask.
好吧好吧  听着
Okay, okay, look. See...
我们不想用武力来解决
...the thing is, we're not gonna fight you guys.
那么这样好了
Here's the deal.
不出去也行  只要你们保证
You won't have to, so long as you never
从今以后不踏入这家咖啡馆
ever show your faces in this coffee house ever again.
你太早把甘瑟抬出来了
I think you played the Gunther card too soon.
菲比  我想你可以过去了
Hey, Pheebs, I think you're good to go.
我不知道
Yeah, I don't know.
又怎么了
What's the matter?
我只是觉得这是个很不好的预兆
I just think that this was a really bad sign.
像是门槛上的野兽啦
Like the beast at the threshold.
我已经没有别的亲人了
It's just I have like no family left, ya know.
除了我外婆之外
except for my grandmother.
可是面对现实吧  她又不会永远都活着
But let's face it, she's not gonna be around forever.
虽然她说她会
Despite what she says.
我有个姐姐
And I have a sister who
但共住一个子宫后  几乎就没说过话了
I've barely spoken to since we shared a womb.
这是我的亲生父亲
I don't know. This is my real father...
我只是希望能一切完美
and I just, I want things to be like just right.
菲比  我完全了解
Yeah Phoebe, I completely understand.
对  随你要怎么样
Yeah, whatever you need.
你要回家吗
Hey, you want to go home?
谢了  对不起
Okay, thanks. Sorry, again.
那是什么
What was that?
我猜现在门槛安全了
I'm guessing the threshold's clear now.
我要买五股SGJ  我现在就要
I want to buy five shares of SGJ and I wanna buy them now.
快点  时间就是金钱啊  朋友
Come on, time is money, my friend!
谢谢
Thank you!
"时间就是金钱啊  朋友"
"Time is money, my friend?"
你错过了  "钱生钱"
You missed "Takes money to make money"
还有  "别逼我过去踢你的华尔街屁股"
and "Don't make me come down there and kick your Wall Street butt."
我早餐前就赚了十七块  你做了什么
I made $ 17 before breakfast. What have you done?
我在这里吃早餐
I had breakfast here,
所以技术上讲我省了三块半
so technically I saved $3.50.
你怎么赚十七块的
How did you make $17?
我的金融白痴朋友
Well, my financially challenged friends
我分别买了些CHP跟ZXY的股票
I split my money and bought some shares of CHP and ZXY.
你怎么选的
How come those?
CHP是因为我暗恋过埃里克·埃斯特拉达
Well, CHP because I used to have a crush on Erik Estrada.
ZXY  因为听起来很"劲"感
And ZXY because I think it sounds "zexy."
那你的MEG呢
What happened to MEG?
MEG帮我赚过钱  但是被我甩了
MEG was good for me, but I dumped her.
我的座右铭是  "在疲软以前撤退"
My motto is, "Get out before they go down."
这绝对不是我的座右铭
That is so not my motto.
菲比  狗怎么样了
Pheebs, how's the dog?
我跟兽医谈过了  纽约州北部的人真好
Okay. I talked to the vet. People are so nice upstate.
他说小家伙不会有问题
Anyway he said the little fella's gonna be okay,
明天我就可以去接它了
I can pick him up tomorrow.
-好极了  -谢天谢地
- Good. - Thank God.
可是他不得不给它缝了好多针
But he did have to have a bunch of stitches.
他还说除非天下红雨
And he said that only once in a blue moon
狗的耳朵才会再长出来
does a dog's ear grow back.
所以还有一点点希望
So still hoping.
菲比  那你现在要打电话告诉你爸
Ok, so Phoebe, now are you going to call your dad
他的狗没事了吗
to let him know that his dog is okay?
我不想在电话里跟我爸相认
I don't want to meet my father over the phone.
我该怎么说  难不成说"我是菲比
What am I gonna say, like "Hi, I'm Phoebe,
被你抛弃的女儿
the daughter you abandoned.
对了  我撞伤了你的狗"
Oh, by the way, I broke your dog."
菲比  你愿意的话  我可以帮你打
Hey, Pheebs, if you want, I'll do it.
好的
Okay.
听着  拜托千万不要提我的事
Listen, just don't say anything about me, okay?
别
Don't...
讲电话太久
... be too long with the phone.
股市收盘以后  她会是个比较好的朋友
She'll be a much better friend once the market closes.
是个女的
It's a woman.
你跟她讲啊
So talk to her.
你好  布菲太太
Hello, Mrs. Buffay.
我知道你的狗在哪里
I know where your dog is.
我要你知道
I want you to know
它会几乎完好如初的还给你
he'll be returned to you almost as good as new...
就在24小时以内
...within 24 hours.
再见
Goodbye.
-干嘛用假声  -很难讲
- Why the voice? - Hard to say.
先生  你的卡布奇诺来了
Your cappuccino, sir.
谢谢
Thank you.
我觉得这里比咖啡馆好多了
Ya know I think this is much better than the coffee house.
对极了
Absolutely.
咖啡粉为什么不化
How come it's not mixing with the water?
包装上说必须要不停地搅拌
Well the package says you have to uh, constantly keep it moving.
一边搅拌一边喝  别让咖啡停下来
Stir and drink, stir and drink, never let it settle.
这太荒唐了吧
This is ridiculous.
这样吧
I'll tell you what.
等我参加完外甥女的洗礼回来后
After I get back from my niece's christening...
我陪你们两个到咖啡馆去
I'll go down to the coffee house with you
我们好好的享受一杯咖啡
and we'll all have a nice cup of coffee alright.
没问题的  有乔伊在
No problem. Joey's there.
好的
Okay.
不
No.
No?
不  我不希望每次想
No! I don't want to have to have Joey with me
喝杯好咖啡  还得有乔伊陪着
every time I want a decent cup of coffee.
我也不想这辈子
Ya know, and I don't wanna spend the rest of my life
喝这种"布卡奇诺"
drinking cappucino with a "K".
我们应该回咖啡馆去  勇敢面对那些人
I say you and I go back down there and stand up to those guys.
好了  先别激动  将军
All right, hang on a second there, Custer.
罗斯  你以前到底有没有被痛扁过
Yeah really, Ross, have you ever been beaten up before?
当然有
Yeah, sure.
-莫妮卡除外  -没有
- By someone besides Monica? - No.
那又怎样  就算被扁又怎么样
So what? So what if we get beaten up,
也许每个男人
maybe that's just something every man
都得经历一次
has to go through once in his life.
就好像取得通过权什么的
Ya know, like a, like a right of passage or somethin’.
再失去一次童贞不行吗
Couldn't we just lose our virginities again?
因为我想我的又长回来了
Ya know, because I think actually mine's growing back.
-借我一百块  -什么
- I need to borrow a hundred bucks. - What?
欢迎回家
Hi, welcome home.
-我需要借一百块  -干嘛
- I need to borrow a hundred bucks. - For what?
我得重回场上继续
I've gotta get back in the game.
你什么时候退场的
Why, when did you get out of the game?
不知道  我赔光了
I don't know, I lost it all ok. I lost it.
-不是吧  -我接受事实了  你也得这样
- No. - Hey, I've come to terms with it, you have to too.
好吧
Okay.
听着  莫妮卡  我很遗憾
Look, Mon, I'm really sorry.
得了得了  你到底借不借
Yeah, yeah, yeah, where are we on the hundred bucks?
我没钱啊
I don't have it.
可是我需要
But I need it!
否则我就得去那个烂馆子工作了
Otherwise I'm gonna have to take that horrible diner job.
你知道的  要跳舞还有穿戏服
You know, with the dancing and the costumes.
我不想穿连火都烧不着的假胸部
I don't want to have to wear flame-retardant boobs.
没人想  亲爱的
Nobody does, honey.
狗狗
Schnoodle!
老天啊  我的狗到底怎么了
Oh, my God. What the hell happened to my dog?
那是个意外
It was an accident.
而且那个肇事的女人
And you know the woman who did this
绝不会蓄意伤害一只狗的
would never ever hurt a dog on purpose.
她吃素
She's a vegetarian.
这是什么  缝线吗
What are these, stitches?
对  8针  对狗来说是56针啦
Yeah, eight of them. That's 56 to him.
还有  下雨的时候
You know also, if, if it's raining,
不要让它抬头太久
you can't let him look up too long,
因为脖套装不了多少水的
'cause that cone'll fill up really really fast.
谢谢你送它的残骸回来
Yeah well, thanks for bringing back what's left of him.
不客气  弗兰克在吗
Sure, oh, is, is Frank home?
你怎么认识他的
How do you know Frank?
那是很久以前的事  他在吗
Just from a long time ago. Is he here?
在
Yeah.
弗兰克
Frank!
来了
Yeah.
什么事啊
What?
我是说  老的弗兰克
Okay, I mean Frank Senior.
他去买日用品了
He went out for groceries.
他会很快回来吗
Okay, will he be back soon?
他四年前去的
He left four years ago.
所以我们猜他随时会回来
So we're expecting him back any minute now.
好吧  那我要走了
Alright, I'm, I'm gonna go.
狗的事很抱歉  对不起
I'm sorry about the dog. Everything.
对不起
I'm sorry.
小姐
Hey, lady!
等一下
Hey, wait up!
-你怎么认识我老爸的   -我不认识他
- How do you know my dad? - Well, I don't really.
基因上认得
Just genetically.
他也算是我老爸吧
He's kind of my dad too.
-不得了  -是啊
- Heavy. - Yeah.
他有没有提过我  菲比
So did he ever talk about me... Phoebe?
没有  不过他一向沉默是金啦
No, but he didn't really talk about anything.
除了高跷
Except stilts.
-高跷   -对啊  他爱高跷
- Stilts? - Yeah, he loved stilts.
有一次我在楼上
There's one time, I was upstairs
偷我妈包里的香烟
I was stealing cigarettes out of my mom's purse
突然间我望了一下
and all of a sudden I look over
看到我爸的头从窗外一上一下地经过
and there's my Dad's head, bobbing past the window.
他脸上满是笑意  还冲我挥手
He just had this big smile on his face and he was waving
因为他踩高跷的时候
'cause he was always happiest
就是他最高兴的时候
when he was on his stilts.
哇
Wow.
是啊
Yeah.
我根本不会踩那玩意儿
I don't know what to do with that.
我也是
Me neither.
所以你是我姐姐吗
So are you, like, my big sister?
是的
Yeah.
真是不得了  你可以请我喝啤酒
This is huge. You can buy me beer!
我不会的
I'm not gonna.
不过知道怎样很酷吗
But you know what's cool though?
如果你有个朋友叫做彼得  那我就可以说
Ok, if you had a friend named Pete, then I could say,
"我认识彼得  他是我弟弟的朋友"
"Oh yeah, I know Pete, he's friends with my brother."
-我有个朋友叫马克  -那也可以啊
- I got a friend named Mark. - That'll work too.
酷  好
Cool. All right.
或许改天我可以打个电话给你
So maybe, you know, I could give you a call sometime.
我们可以好好聊聊或什么的
We could talk or something.
-好啊  那样很好  -好
- Yeah, that'd be okay. - All right.
-电话簿上有我的电话  -好的
- I'm in the book. - Okay.
那就这样了
All right.
喜欢高跷啊
So stilts, huh?
你想的话  我可以带你去后面
Yeah hey, you know if you want I can take you around back
看他头撞到排雨沟的那个地方
and show you where he hit his head on the rain gutter.
好的
Okay.
我们办到了  我们在这儿
We did it. We're here.
我们立场坚定
We are standing our ground.
一杯咖啡到底要煮多久啊
How long does a cup of coffee take?
快点  快点呀
Would you come on? Come on!
谢谢
Thank you.
好了  喝完了
Ah, there we go.
我们已经证明了自己的观点
I think we proved our point.
-烫到嘴了没  -舌头没感觉了
- You burn your mouth? - Cannot feel my tongue.
恶霸  大恶霸
Bullies! Big bullies!
看看谁来了  是胆小鬼们
Look who's here. It's the weenies.
我们那天讲得不够清楚吗
Did we not make ourselves clear the other day?
清楚  所以我们才来
Yes. That's why we're here.
对  我们在坚守立场
Yes, we're standing our ground.
你也看的出来吧
Apparently.
少说废话了
Let's do this already.
慢着  你那是什么  武器吗
Woah, ho-ho, whad'ya got there, a weapon?
一只好表  我可不想在揍你时弄坏了
A nice watch. I don't want to break it on your ribs.
好的  来吧
All right, let's do this.
我有问题  如果我不在乎我的表
Question: If I don't care about my watch,
我可以拿来当武器吗
can I use it as a weapon?
-什么意思  -很锋利  金属做的
- What do you mean? - It's sharp, it's metal.
我想这可以用来  发挥很大的杀伤力
I think I can do some you know serious damage with it.
-不  你不能用手表  -好吧
- No, you can't use your watch. - Okay.
-钥匙也不行  -好吧
- Or your keys. - Okay.
听我说  这样好了
Look, here's what we'll do.
把所有的钥匙和手表
We'll put all keys and watches
都放在这个帽子里  摆在那里
in the hat over there.
好吗
All right?
好了  伙计们  来吧
All right, come on, man. Let's do it!
趁我还记得  脸可以打吗
Before I forget, are we hitting faces?
当然可以打  为什么不能打脸
Of course we're hitting faces, why wouldn't you hit faces?
因为我周一得上班  有个重要的演讲
Well because I have to work on Monday, I have a big presentation.
事实上  我明天要带人去看房子
Actually, you know, uh, I gotta show this apartment tomorrow
所以不打脸这个主意  其实也不赖
and uh, you know, this no faces thing might not be a bad idea.
-脖子以上不准打  -好的
- Ok, nothing from the neck up. - All right.
腰部以下也不行
Or the waist down.
-黛娜在排卵期  -真的  你们又在试了
- Dana's ovulating. - Really? You guys trying again?
好吧  让我先搞清楚
Ok, so let me just get this straight.
我们只能打中间的部分吗
So we're strictly talking about the middle?
来呀
Come on!
想挨揍吗  想试试厉害吗
You want some of this, huh? You want a piece of this, huh?
我就在这里
I'm standin here, huh.
那俩家伙偷了我们的东西
Those guys are taking our stuff!
让开  小心
Get away, look out.
天啊  太不可思议了  了不起
God, that was amazing. That was incredible.
-你们好厉害  -我们  那你们呢
- You guys, you guys kicked butt. - Us, what about you guys?
你们真的  给了那个老贼颜色瞧了
Man you really, bing, gave it to old Mr. Clean back there.
-那家伙长得好壮啊  -没错  不是吗
- He was a big guy. - Yeah, he was, wasn't he?
是呀  我不知道  我全错过了
Yeah, I wouldn't know having missed everything.
不要太苛责自己了
Don't do that to yourself.
我们都有可能被那个小女孩的跳绳给绊倒
Any one of us could have tripped over that little girl's jump rope.
对了  两位  那我们
So listen, guys we are uh,
没事了吧
are we okay here?
没事了
We're okay.
那帽子可以还给我了吗
Okay, so can I have my hat back?
不行
No.
天哪  看看她
Oh, my God. Look at her.
莫妮卡
Hi, Monica!
顺利吗
How's it going?
好美的胸哦
Hey, nice boobs.
各位  看看这个
Guys, guys. Check this out.
太棒了
Excellent.